<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on ocfox&#39;s den</title>
    <link>https://ocfox.me/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on ocfox&#39;s den</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.5</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ocfox.me/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t worry about future</title>
      <link>https://ocfox.me/posts/dont-care-future/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ocfox.me/posts/dont-care-future/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Excessive worry about the future drops me into a cycle of anxiety.
When I moved to the next station, these emotions stuck in my feet like a quagmire.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;dont-worry&#34;&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t Worry&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There&amp;rsquo;s no need to worry about what you will fucked up.
Even if it happens, look forward, nothing will change if you pay for that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Forest, where I am. I want to follow pure instinct like a tiger, a dog, or even an ant.
Eating when hungry, drinking when thirsty, enjoying music, enjoying the fresh air, paying attention to things around self.
Anyway, don&amp;rsquo;t tie up hands by life.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Waste time cure my life</title>
      <link>https://ocfox.me/posts/the-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://ocfox.me/posts/the-time/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Music like time travel takes me into the past or future,
waste too.
What is waste? It&amp;rsquo;s some blurred concept.
Maybe I want to get something but I don&amp;rsquo;t work for that,
is this a kind of waste?
Gradually, I compromise — compromise to life, to what I need,
to what I want, and to everything I think in the past.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now I only follow what I could get instead of what I want to.
What&amp;rsquo;s the meaning of my thinking? Is this a kind of waste? Sometimes,
I remind myself that I can&amp;rsquo;t waste too much time, it will kill my life.
After these things, I enjoy wasting time, I call that enjoy the time, and enjoy life, if something I did and get happy, why not?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
